https://www.crowleycheese.com/privacy-notice.html

|  800.683.2606
Privacy Notice
Effective Date: November 10, 2018
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Crowley Cheese LLC and our websites; https://crowleycheese.com and https://store.crowleycheese.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by these websites, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:
What information we collect;
With whom it is shared;
How it can be corrected;
How it is secured;
How policy changes will be communicated; and
How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on these sites. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email or postal mail in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any;
Change/correct any data we have about you;
Have us delete any data we have about you;
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Sharing
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon on your web browser, or by looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Notification of Changes
Whenever a material change is made to our privacy policy, we will notify you of the change via email.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (802)-259-2340 or via email at: galen@crowleycheese.com.
Home
Order Crowley Cheese!
Order Online
Mail-In Order Form
All About Crowley Cheese
Our Cheeses
What Makes It Special?
Crowley Cheese Receives 2014 Editors' Choice Award in Yankee Magazine
Connect
Be the first to know about special deals, new recipes, tastings, and more! Join our mailing list:
Email:
©2020 Crowley Cheese, LLC | All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
800.683.2606
